<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Micael Reis</title>
    <description>Just a personal website of a Software Engineer
</description>
    <link>https://micaelreis.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://micaelreis.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 17:51:07 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 17:51:07 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello! Welcome To My Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there, my name is Micael Reis, I’m a software engineer from Portugal and I would like to welcome you to my blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://media.giphy.com/media/cE02lboc8JPO/giphy.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Hello there&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A long time ago I had this idea of creating a website where I could showcase my projects and share my experience. Unfortunately, I never got around to do it and as time was going by I started to forget about this idea, until &lt;strong&gt;NOW!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot; style=&quot;font-weight: 200;&quot;&gt;It happened! It finally happened! I created my personal website and blog. YEYYY!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the website will serve as a way to show the projects I have been working in and the volunteer work I have done recently, the goal of this blog is to share the thoughts and experiences that I will encounter during my professional life as a Software Engineer / Web Developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this blog, expect to see a lot of technical posts as well as some personal posts related to my work experience. For the technical posts, I will be more focused on web technologies and frameworks since that is my field of work, but I will not hesitate to write about other cool things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot; style=&quot;font-weight: 200;&quot;&gt;I can't promise I will upload frequently, but I can promise you that I will do my best to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in knowing how I developed this website, I did it with the help of &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and hosted it on &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt;. You can check the source code on my GitHub page, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/micaelpreis/micaelpreis.github.io&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more, BYEE!!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://micaelreis.com/2016/10/04/hello.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://micaelreis.com/2016/10/04/hello.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
